When family cannot be here
亲人朋友  未能相见
Havin' journeyed far and wide
仍旧还远行在外
We sing a song to honor them
高声歌颂  一同怀念
To remember days gone by
回忆往日不复返
So take your cup and raise it high
来吧朋友  高举酒杯
Just as surely I'll do mine
只为个痛快开怀
And laugh we will at stories told
津津乐道  往日故事
As we smile at days gone by
笑对昔日不复返
For family not here, my dears
亲人朋友  不在身边
Havin' journeyed far and wide
仍旧还远行在外
For loyalty and kindness both
真诚和善  由衷笑面
We smile at days gone by
那往日不再还
Our paths will cross again one day
命运路上  终会相见
In time to re-unite
我们将再相会
For family is always near
只因家人  终伴身旁
Even when the seas are wide
又怎怕  远隔沧海
So take your cup and raise it high
来吧朋友  高举酒杯
Just as surely I'll do mine
只为个痛快开怀
And make a toast for family
举杯欢庆  祝福家人
And the tales of days gone by
和那往日不复还
For family not here, my dears
亲人朋友  不在身边
Havin' journeyed far and wide
仍旧还远行在外
For loyalty and kindness both
真诚和善 由衷笑面
Take joy at days gone by
那昔日不再还
For loyalty and kindness both
真诚和善  由衷笑面
We smile at days gone by
那往日不再来
翻译
轮回
润色
无敌超人  Leo Dango
校对
森林金雨  Loadhe
背景图绘制
Luka
时间轴
BronyDee  Loadhe
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看